# RUEI-PU(Allen) KOU

imakou@gmail.com I (905)-966-3228 I Works - git.io/v5USD

4+ years of experience in front-end development(RWD, SPA). I have 2 years working experience of developing medium projects of web applications by React.js and others tools such as Git and Docker to enhance my developing performance. I also have experience with Serverless structure (AWS' Lambda and API Gateway). Currently, React.js and Redux are the major frameworks I am using in my projects.

## Skills

- 4+ yrs HTML / CSS (Sass)
- 2+ yrs React/ Redux(ES6)
- 1+ yrs NodeJs
- Mocha Selenium Serverless
- Webpack Gulp Git Docker

# Work experiences

#### Web Developer I Gelenk Network Inc

Markham, Canada I Sep 2017 - Present

- · Implemented web apps based on React and Redux and API based on Node.js and GCP
- · Web Message APP
  - · Realtime sending and receiving SMS or MMS
  - · Nice and modern UI implemented by Material UI
  - Highly friendly UX including auto-saving drafts and creating message templates
- GenVoice Portal Telefone configuration CMS
  - · Visualizing usages as pie and line charts by BizChart.
  - · Exporting bills as the formatted PDF file
  - · IVR(Interactive Voice Response) system with a visual keypad

### Front End Developer I University of Waterloo - Conrad Business Centre

Waterloo, Canada I May 2017 - Aug 2017

- · Implemented features based on React and Redux
- Practiced features including dynamic data graph, real-time chatting (Twilio's API)
- Built BDD testing practices (e2e by Cucumber, Selenium and Mocha)
- Cooperated with UI/UX team and enhanced website's components to be better

#### Front End Developer I DIGIM

Taipei, Taiwan I January 2014 to May 2014

- · Developed retina display friendly RWD pages
- · Collaborated with the creative and back-end teams
- Enhanced colleagues' developing performances by using Sass and HTML template(ERB)

#### Web Developer I Rexholiday

Taipei, Taiwan I July 2013 to December 2013

- · Collaborated with stakeholders to improve an internal traveling system
- · Developed internal IT devices plan
- · Enhanced colleagues' workflow using SaaS

#### Web Developer I Webike.tw

Taipei, Taiwan I January 2013 to July 2013

- Designed and developed the first version of prototype of eCommerce website base on Magento
- Organized over 300k primitive data to MySQL database
- · Deployed project to EC2 instances in LAMP environment on AWS
- · Made back-up plans and optimized servers' performances

## Education

Diploma in Computer Programmer Seneca College - Toronto, ON January 2015 to April 2017

Bachelor in Information management Hsing Wu University - Taipei, Taiwan August 2007 to August 2011

# **Activity**

## Volunteer I Fa-Yi Chong-De Guang-Hui Association

Toronto, Canada I April 2014 to Present

- Assisted members to run meetings using live streaming platform
- Educated charity member on selection and implementation of electronic devices
- Organizing meeting records and distributed records to members